A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Librarian of Virginia, 1832-2024 Jan
Library of Virginia
- 2007-2024 (Accession 54082)., 14.35 cu. ft. (41 boxes)
  - Library Board.
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2021 June 28. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2021 Sept 13. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2022 Jan 10. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2022 Apr 11. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2022 June 27. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2022 Sept 19. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2023 Jan 23. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2023 Apr 17. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2023 June 26. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2023 Sept 18. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation, 2024 Jan 8. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation - Board Handbook, 2013-2014. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation - Board Handbook, 2014-2015. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation - Board Handbook, 2015-2016. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation - Board Handbook, 2016-2017. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 720 Agendas and supporting documentation - Board Handbook, 2018-2019. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 730 Correspondence with the Library Board, 2007-2008. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 730 Correspondence with the Library Board, 2009-2011. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 730 Correspondence with the Library Board, 2012-2014. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 730 Correspondence with the Library Board, 2015-2017. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 730 Correspondence with the Library Board, 2018-2023. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 740 Correspondence of the Library Board, 2008-2010. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - 780 Patron of Letters, 2016-2024. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Other Board, Commission and Committee Records.
    These records document the State Librarian's involvement in outside boards, counciles, commissions and committees including the Library Advisory Council, State Historical Records Advisory Board, Virginia Bicentennial of the Americal War of 1812 Commission, Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission, Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council and the Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission. Records may include meeting agendas, minutes and supporting documentation, such as articles, brochures, correspondence, proposals and reports.
    - 810 Library Advisory Council (SCHEV), 2007-2022. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 820 State Historical Records Advisory Board (SHRAB), 2007-2018. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2008 Dec 18. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2009 June 17. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2009 Sept 21. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2010 Jan 6. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2010 Aug 17. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2010 Oct 19. (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2010 Dec 8. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2011 Feb 9. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2011 July 18. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2011 Nov 17. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2012 Sept 19. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission - Legacy Symposium Subcommittee, 2013 Aug 5. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission - Legacy Symposium Subcommittee (Workgroups - Programs and Education; Logistics), 2013 Aug 21. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission - Legacy Symposium Subcommittee (Workgroups - Programs and Education; Logistics), 2013 Oct 23. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission - Legacy Symposium Subcommittee (Workgroups - Programs and Education; Logistics), 2013 Nov 26. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission - Legacy Symposium (event), 2014 June 19-21. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2014 July 9. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - 830 Virginia Bicentennial of the American War of 1812 Commission, 2014 Dec 8. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - 835 World War II Commission, 2015 Dec 10. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - 835 World War I and World War II Commission, 2016 Apr 14. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - 840 Virginia American Revolution 250th Commission, 2022 July 6. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - 840 Virginia American Revolution 250th Commission, 2022 Sept 21. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - 840 Virginia American Revolution 250th Commission, 2023 Jan 6. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Correspondence, 2007-2016. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission, 2007 Jan 9. (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Advisory Council, 2007 Mar 27. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission, 2007 Apr 19. (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Workgroup 3 (Education), 2007 Aug 15. (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Executive Committee, 2007 Nov 16. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Workgroup 3 (Education), 2007 Nov 16. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission, 2007 Nov 28. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission, 2008 June 10. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Workgroup 3 (Education), 2008 Oct 9. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission, 2009 Nov 9. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Executive Committee, 2010 Oct 12. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Executive Committee, 2011 May 16. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 850 Virginia Sesquicentennial of the Amercian Civil War Commission - Executive Committee, 2012 May 22. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 860 Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Commission - Invitation, 2015 July 6. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2007 July 12. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2008 Dec 1. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2009 Apr 27. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2011 May 3. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2011 July 18. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2012 May 23. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2012 Aug 21. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2012 Dec 17. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2013 Dec 5. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Records Subcommittee, 2014 July 8. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2014 Sept 16. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2014 Nov 18. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2015 May 20. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2015 Sept 30. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2015 Nov 18. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2016 June 23. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2016 Sept 19. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2016 Oct 17. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2016 Nov 21. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2016 Dec 5. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2017 May 15. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2017 Aug 14. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2017 Nov 20. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2018 Apr 4. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Remedies Subcommittee, 2018 May 21. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Records Subcommittee, 2018 May 21. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Remedies Subcommittee, 2018 June 4. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Records Subcommittee, 2018 June 27. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Records Subcommittee, 2018 Aug 8. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2018 Aug 22. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2018 Oct 17. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2019 May 8. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2018 July 15. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2018 July 17. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Phishing Study Subcommittee, 2019 Aug 21. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2019 Sept 18. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council - Phishing Study Subcommittee, 2019 Oct 8. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2019 Dec 4. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2020 Nov 17. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2021 Apr 28. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2021 June 19. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2021 Nov 10. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2022 June 6. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2022 Oct 3. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2022 Dec 14. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - 870 Virginia Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Advisory Council, 2023 Dec 4. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2011 Mar 29. (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2011 June 14. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2011 Nov 21. (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2012 May 22. (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2012 July 12. (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2012 Aug 23. (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2012 Dec 13. (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2013 Mar 20. (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2013 Oct 21. (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2014 Feb 17. (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2014 Dec 8. (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2015 Jan 12. (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2015 June 26. (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2015 Oct 1. (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2016 June 27. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2016 July 20. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2016 Oct 5. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2016 Nov 16. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - March to Mother's Day strategy meeting, 2017 Feb 1. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2017 Mar 21. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2017 June 21. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Excutive Committee, 2017 Sept 14. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Exeutive Committee, 2017 Oct 10. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2017 Oct 24. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Groundbreaking Ceremony, 2017 Dec 4. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2018 Jan 4. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2018 Feb 28. (Box 36, 13 13)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission, 2018 June 20. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2018 Aug 31. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2019 Jan 3. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2019 May 23. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Executive Committee, 2021 May 27. (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Correspondence, 2011-2019. (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Dedication Ceremony, 2019 Oct 14. (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Impact 100 Big Give Presentation, 2016 May 16. (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Making Women's History in Virginia Conference, 2016 Sept 23. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Miscellaneous, 2010-2019; undated. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Overview Notebook, 2016. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - 890 Women of Virginia Commemorative Commission / Virginia Women's Monument Commission - Richmond Committee, Friends of History - Monument to Women in Capitol Square, undated. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous.
    These records include miscellaneous invitations.
    - 930 Invitations (miscellaneous), 2007-2012. (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - 930 Invitations (miscellaneous), 2013-2024. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Associations.
    XX
    - 1020 American Library Association (ALA) 20. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - 1030 Association of Southeastern Research Libraries (ASERL) 2009-2015. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2009 Jan 23. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2009 May 13. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2009 Oct 26-28. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2011 Oct 21-26. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2012 Apr 25. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2014 Oct 19-22. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2016 Jan 8. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2016 May 4. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2017 May 3. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA) - Measures that matter, 2017 Sept 19-20. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2017 Oct 29-Nov 1. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA), 2018 Oct 31. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - 1040 Chief Officers of State Library Agencies (COSLA) - Miscellaneous, 2007-2023. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - 1041 Council of State Archivists (COSA) - Correspondence, 2013-2016. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - 1041 Council of State Archivists (COSA), 2014 Aug 11-16. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - 1041 Council of State Archivists (COSA) (with SAA), 2016 Aug 2-6. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - 1041 Council of State Archivists (COSA), 2017 July 12. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 1041 Council of State Archivists (COSA), 2018 Aug 15. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - 1041 Council of State Archivists (COSA) (with NAGARA and SAA), 2018 Aug 12-19. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - 1050 OCLC, 2009-2018. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - 1060 Friends of the Virginia State Archives, 2007-2016. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - 1070 Virginia Library Association, 2007-2012. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - 1080 Virginia Public Library Directors Association (VPLDA), 2008-2023. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - 1090 Virginia Coalition for Open Government (VCOG), 2007. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - 1100 Lyrasis, 20. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - 1110 Richmond Area Museum Directors, 2008; 2020. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - 1120 Genealogical societies, 2007-2023. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - 1180 Southern Council of State Library Agencies, 2007-2023. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - 11 Virginia Foundation for the Humanities, 2008-2019. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - 1180 Richmond Academic Library Consortium (RALC), 2013-2020. (Box 39, Folder 12)